I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
- Let me help you with that.
- It's okay, man.
- Wait. Let... let me...
- It's fine. Just leave it.
I loved that movie.
Classic movies are the best.
You fell asleep.
That's how you can tell
I liked it.
So, listen, um, turns out my old band
is playing a gig downtown tonight.
- Do you wanna go?
- Your old band? You were in a band?
- I never told you I was in a band?
- No, no. What did you play?
- Bass. Vocals.
- Ah, you are so cool.
- Let's go.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay, then. We need a cab.
Hey.
About that question.
Was that "do you like butter with your
popcorn" or "will you come with me to D.C."?
D.C.
Oh, I just wanted you to know
I've been thinking about it really hard
and I-I wanna say yes.
It's just... I've been
so independent my whole life.
- It's a big decision for me.
- I understand one hundred percent.
Take your time.
There's no deadline.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So, you gonna get onstage
and sing?
- Sorry.
- Uh...
Yeah.
- Jane, this better be important.
- "Yes, it is."
I am heading south on trinity
between 6th and 7th.
- I need backup fast.
- W-what's going on?
A girl's been abducted.
- What's going on?
- Okay, so...
I went to buy some tacos
at that great truck on Juarez.
- You know the one?
- Yeah.
Anyhow, I bumped into this big
guy. He drops his shopping bags.
And it's obvious from what spilled out
that he's keeping a woman captive.
So I followed him.
He went in there, in that guest house.
Now, normally, I would take care of this
but this guy's sketchy.
What was in
the shopping bags?
All sorts of stuff...
duct tape, women's vitamins.
You brought me out here
for duct tape?
You need to trust me.
There is something off
about this guy.
I mean, who buys nudie magazines
and tiger beat?
You know what?!
You're a jerk!
I was on a date, and you knew it
and you did this to screw it up.
- You were on a date?
- Yeah.
And I am an idiot just for listening to you.
I'm gonna go see a band.
No, t-there is a woman in there
that doesn't wanna be
and she's possibly injured,
all right?
I will bet you anything you like
that I am right.
I'll bet you
a million dollars.
Fine.
What?! What?!
Sir, we're with the FBI.
Do you have a female in there with you?
Female? No.
No. No females.
No females here. I know you.
I know you. Don't lie to my friend.
She's a very serious person.
What's your problem, man?
I'm not lying.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Hey! Y...
This is agent Lisbon
with the FBI! Where are you?
Stay there.
She's been shot.
Put your hands
on your head!
- I-I didn't do nothing.
- Put them on your head!
She's really cold.
I need emergency medical
assistance at 812 Ashcroft.
It's a guest house
at the end of the drive.
I was tryna fix her.
T-that's why I went to the store.
Get down slowly.
It's gonna be all right.
We have a doctor coming.
I'm gonna get a doctor.
You're gonna be okay.
Just look at me.
Look at me. I'm here.
Bow and arrow.
What does that mean,
"bow and arrow"?
I ain't speaking
no more.
Just look at me.
Breathe.
It's okay.
Breathe, breathe.
Come on.
Just breathe.
Jane, she's gone.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Mr. Delahay.
I need to understand how that girl
wound up in your bed, bleeding to death.
I was tryna make her better.
I didn't mean no harm.
- Except you shot her, didn't you?
- No, I did not. I don't do that.
I fix things...
things others throw away.
"I find new uses for them."
"And I found her like that, and
I was gonna make her better"
"till you people interrupted."
"She died because of you,
not because of me."
Okay, well,
you say you found her.
When was that?
It was early last night
and I was out driving on route 16.
That's how I find things, mostly.
And that girl...
someone thought she was garbage.
But I knew better.
You have a history
of stalking girls, huh?
Restraining orders
in Idaho and Nevada.
Now, that's lies and
bureaucracy, is what that is.
I'm just...
I'm just trying...
I didn't shoot nobody, never.
"Now, you say you found
this girl on route 16."
Where exactly?
I don't know!
I don't remember!
I was drinking! I...
I was... I was drunk.
Okay, well, if...
if we, uh, show you a map
Would that help?
Maps...
don't give me maps.
I know all about your maps.
That is one crazy individual.
He has no idea what he did.
I think he does.
His world view is meticulously
constructed brick by brick.
And we didn't find a gun.
No registered weapon.
No gun in the house.
- No residue either.
- No.
But there was blood
in his truck.
So you think we should
believe his story?
A man goes for a drive
on route 16
finds a gutshot girl,
and brings her home?
- Yeah.
Her name is Leanne Cole,
20 years old. We ran her fingerprints.
She was arrested for shoplifting
two years ago in Spokane.
She was also arrested for
driving with an expired license.
She tried to evade.
It was a misdemeanor.
So, joyriding.
Looks like. Her parents died
when she was in high school.
Her aunt said
that she dropped out of school
And moved
down to Los Angeles.
I'm gonna go talk to her roommate
find out what she was doing in Texas.
"What I don't get is how she got
back to the U.S. already."
"They just left for Europe
four days ago."
- For Europe.
- "Yeah. Like Italy and stuff."
- Who? Leanne and some guy?
- "Yeah, but it wasn't like that."
"Leanne wasn't a party girl."
"I know a lot of girls
who get taken all over."
"This was professional.
She booked a modeling gig."
And they left
four days ago?
"Yeah. Some model scout
set it up."
Did you meet this guy...
the model scout?
"No, I didn't.
I think his name is Jesse."
No e-mails, no texts
with anyone named Jesse.
And we're still waiting
on her phone records, right?
Yeah, but here's the weird thing...
She leaves for a modeling gig
four days ago
and her digital life
just disappears... nothing.
Delahay says he found her last night.
There's a three-day gap.
So who was she with?
Where's this model scout?
Someone shot her and dumped her
on route 16.
- We don't even know where yet.
- We're working on that.
Jane's gonna jog
Delahay's memory.
Mind if I join you?
Can't stop you.
I can't even
scratch an itch.
Let me help you
with that.
Let me see.
All right.
Just hold still.
Thank you.
You say you don't remember
where you found Leanne Cole.
I think
you do remember.
So you think I'm a liar, too.
No. I just don't think
you can find the memory.
Huh.
Like beer?
Who doesn't like beer?
There you go.
- Mm. That's good, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
Now, Thaddeus,
I want you to imagine
that you're driving along
route 16 last night.
Okay.
Might be easier
if you close your eyes.
Now you're in your truck.
Nice ice-cold beer
in the cupholder.
You're about to turn
onto route 16.
It's dark, warm.
What do you hear?
Jazz, man.
Jazz on the radio, huh?
You mind turning that down
a little?
Thanks.
Now I can talk quietly.
The music's still playing.
You're about to turn right
onto route 16.
You can feel
the road change.
Tell me what you see.
Um... there's, uh...
Nothing at first.
Live oak tree on the right.
Found an old miner's lamp there.
Took it home, fixed it up.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
"I'm... I'm driving."
"Yeah."
"There... there's an old
gas station around mile two."
"Turnoff for quint's farm."
"They let me come
and haul stuff."
"A little creek...
But... It... it is dry now."
"Then... then,
there's an old bar."
"It's empty now, and..."
- she's there.
- You can see her?
She's all dusty, bleeding.
"I-I... I can smell her hair."
"It smells like dirt."
Bingo.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I got some Thai from that place
over on South Congress.
- I love that place.
- I know.
You're good.
Mm... Not really.
I have an ulterior motive.
- Oh?
- Just tryna make D.C. Look attractive.
Are they opening
a restaurant there?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Hey, agent Pike.
Ah! From your favorite Thai place
on South Congress. That's a shame.
- Why?
- We gotta go. We have a location.
- The girl?
- The girl.
I'm driving.
I'll meet you downstairs.
Oh, office scuttlebutt says
that your new guy
is ditching us for the D.C. office
and maybe you're going with him.
Oh. Well,
who told you about that?
Well, you know,
I hear about things.
Are you going with him?
We'd miss you.
To be honest, sir,
I don't know.
Hmm. What does Jane
have to say about this?
Well, if he wants to talk
about it, he can.
But he hasn't,
so I'm sure he's fine with it.
- Well, maybe he doesn't know.
- He's Jane. Of course he knows.
- Remember, Jane is a psychic.
- A pretend psychic.
If you haven't told him,
chances are he doesn't know.
Delahay was driving east
so he would have picked her up
on the south side of the street.
So, south we should walk.
Someone could have dumped
her from a truck.
Or she was shot here.
Her hair smelled of dirt.
Her shoes were caked in clay.
She walked, collapsed.
He found her.
We better be getting a move on.
This is wide-open country.
Well, she was bleeding badly.
She couldn't have gone too far.
Voilà.
Tractor trailer.
Looks like some sort of way station
for undocumented immigrants.
We're pretty far north for that.
I'm gonna wait outside.
Lisbon!
- What?
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Listen.
You hear it?
We need to move that.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Daniela.
You ready for me?
I guess.
Look, I know this is hard.
But any detail you have
will help us find who did this to you.
Can I sit?
Did you find my sister?
Your sister?
You have to find her.
Is this her?
No.
- Do you recognize her?
- No. My sister's Amy Welker.
She's 16.
You have to find her.
- She was abducted with you?
- Yes.
We're gonna do everything we can
to find your sister.
You need to tell me
everything you know.
Me and Amy...
We did some modeling,
like little things, you know?
We answered an ad online
for an open casting call.
They took our head shots.
The guy told us
to come back.
- Wait. The photographer?
- No, the... the model scout.
His name was Jesse.
He said that clothing designers
in Europe
would love us
for their shows.
Did he say where
in Europe?
No.
He just said to bring
our passports and clothes
and everything else
they'd take care of.
Jesse gave us
a glass of champagne
and made a toast
to our new adventure together.
Next thing...
I woke up.
And I was in that place.
One last question, Daniela.
Do the words "bow and arrow"
mean anything to you?
The girl we found said that
right before she died.
Did Jesse ever say
those words to you?
No. Why?
Just asking.
It's okay.
We're gonna do our best
to find your sister.
Her sister was there.
There are more girls.
- "We know."
- You know?
Forensics is
at the safe house now.
They found DNA from 20 different
people on those water bottles.
- "20 girls?"
- Or more.
She had the same story...
the phony model scout, this Jesse guy.
Someone is rounding up
these girls.
Yeah. But where'd
they take them?
We have approximately 20 young
females abducted by traffickers.
We found fresh tractor-trailer
marks at the scene.
So we figure these girls are on a truck
with an 18-hour head start on us.
And since they're traffickers it's logical
to assume they headed to Mexico.
Nuevo Laredo is where
they would most likely cross.
The Laredo world trade port of entry.
Straight shot down I-35.
But the truck left
at least 18 hours ago.
Which means they could be a thousand
miles into Mexico by now.
- Possible but not probable.
- No?
Well, when the truck left the house
it was headed due north, right?
So, uh, last time I looked,
Mexico was the other way.
So, you think
they're headed to Oklahoma?
That's not exactly a hot spot
for sex-slave trafficking.
True, so they headed north
for some other reason...
- Pick up more girls, probably.
- It's possible.
Yeah, you can fit a lot more
than 20 girls in a freight container.
More like 40.
But not for long.
So by now, they're probably
headed south to Mexico
straight down the I-35,
probably as we speak...
Well, possibly.
Too thin to warrant
closing down a highway.
And that's what we would need
in order to search every truck.
Hmm. Yeah.
Well, we don't need to set up
a real road block.
We just need to convince the driver
of that truck that we've set up a roadblock.
Sorry... scanning long-range
frequencies is like...
- I don't have a metaphor. It's hard.
- "Heads up on a 10-42."
"Traffic jam's backed up across
the border there at Nuevo Laredo."
"Thanks a lot, Heavy Metal."
Places, everyone.
"This is lefty here.
Heads up."
"I'm hearing highway patrol set up
a checkpoint right near the border on I-35."
Over.
"Yep. They pulled me over,
checked my cab and my cargo."
"And these aren't county Mounties.
These are some full-grown bears."
"Big Pete jumping in
with a 10-17."
"Company driver said smokey's
set up on the southbound side"
"about yardstick 21."
"They eyeballed him, but he's deadheading
so they waved him through."
What?
That was incredible.
"10-4, big Pete.
Thanks for the heads up."
"I'll pass that along.
Over."
I believe you hooked him, big Pete.
I believe you hooked him.
I'm gonna pull off at that diner
right north of Laredo
and make sure the cab's shipshape
before I hit that bear trap.
- It's crowded.
- Yes, it is.
- How do we know if it worked?
- Oh, it worked.
You think all these people got off the roads
because they're scared of cops?
Well, not all of them.
Just the ones that have something to hide.
Well, how can we tell
which one's our driver?
We look.
- What about those two?
- The lady? I don't think so.
Not just her.
The two of them.
They're obviously
traveling together.
They're not a couple.
There's no intimacy there.
Oh, they've been in a truck for hours.
How could there be intimacy?
I'll show you.
- Ohh!
- Oh, sorry.
What was that about?
Well, I bumped her, and he didn't
say anything. They're not a couple.
He's got a gun in his jacket.
Go get them, guys.
You okay?
- FBI!
- Cut your engine!
Lady!
It's all right, ladies. We're
with the FBI. You're safe now.
Hi, Daniela.
I'm special agent Kimball Cho
with the FBI.
We just stopped a truck that was
transporting girls into Mexico.
Was my sister on it?
No, I'm sorry.
We didn't find your sister.
But we're still looking.
Don't worry.
Now, I've interviewed the girls
from the truck
and their descriptions match yours
regarding the modeling scam.
We've made a composite sketch
from your description and theirs
of the modelling scout.
Does this look like the man
you and your sister met with?
Yes!
That's Jesse.
Okay. Thank you.
It's a big help.
Agent Cho!
Find my sister, please.
- She's just a kid.
- Okay.
Are the girls all right?
Are they safe?
Do you recognize
either of those girls?
No.
That's Amy Welker.
She's 16 years old.
She might have been
on the other truck.
- The other truck?
- Yeah. They left the day before we did.
Those girls are
well over the border by now.
- Who is the driver?
- I never met him.
What happened to the girls
after they were delivered?
I don't know.
I'm not a bad person.
I really need you to believe that.
Why should I?
The bank was gonna foreclose
on my parents' house
so I agreed to drive
some illegals over the border.
It didn't seem so bad,
you know?
- It's still against the law.
- I know
and that's what I said,
too, after the one trip.
They told me they'd
turn me over to the police
unless I started driving trucks
full of girls the other way into Mexico.
How did you get the girls
over the border?
A border guard...
he'd been paid off.
- He'd recognize the truck.
- How?
There's a dashboard ornament
in my cab.
It was provided
by the guys in Mexico...
A hula dancer.
What about the girl
who ran off... Leanne Cole.
- She got away?
- She's dead.
I was really hoping
she got away.
We were running late.
"Ramon was pissed."
Please!
Get in there. It's okay. It's okay.
You're doing good. You're doing good.
We're 45 minutes behind!
What the hell, Claudia?!
Relax, Ramon.
We'll make it up on the road.
Come on! Speed it up!
- Claudia, go get her!
- Me?!
Go!
Go find her now!
Come on!
- Where is she?
- I don't know!
I don't see her.
We're an hour behind.
Get to the truck.
Come on. We gotta go.
He started making calls,
telling people what happened.
- Who did he call?
- I don't know.
But I never saw him so scared.
He was worried
she'd go to the police?
No. Ramon wasn't scared
of the cops.
It was the guy he worked for
that scared the hell out of him.
- Do you know his name?
- I just know Ramon
and the guys
we turned the girls over to.
Did you get their names?
Yeah. The Qasimi brothers,
Ali and Ray.
This is Ray and Ali Qasimi.
They're businessmen with
connections to the Middle East and Asia.
Raised and Educated in the U.S.
they have a network of assets worldwide.
I checked with Washington,
put in a call to Interpol
and there's nothing
on these guys.
They're as clean
as a whistle.
How are we doing with the leads
from the girls?
The modeling agencies all pulled
up stakes after Ramon's call.
All that's left
are empty storefronts.
We're tryna track backwards
through phone records
and rental agreements
but I don't think we're gonna get much.
It was
a well-run organization.
Okay, what about Ramon's cellphone?
Is there anything that we can use?
It was a prepaid cell.
All the calls he made
went to burner phones, as well.
Okay.
Does anyone have any good news
that they can offer up?
Well, all the women ID'd
the same model agent.
Called himself Jesse.
We had a drawing made.
Wylie's running it through
the facial-recognition database.
Um, I think I just got a hit, actually.
There's a James O'connor
in San Diego
Who's a really close match...
also goes by Jesse.
I'm sending cops
to check on him.
Okay. Well, that's good news.
Anyone else?
Can't we bring
the Qasimis in?
The driver will testify
against them.
They're in Mexico with no criminal record
and a ticking clock.
By the time we get an extradition order
they'll be long gone.
And I don't think we can get them
to come to the states for us.
- Do we still have the driver's truck?
- Yeah. It's impounded.
But according to the Qasimis,
it's just late.
- I bet they're getting anxious now.
- And?
- Well, that's our in.
- How's that?
You and I are gonna drive
that truck down to Mexico
and we're gonna talk those Qasimis
into doing a deal with us.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
I do.
What do you say?
Maybe this wasn't
such a good idea.
No. I think
it looks good on you.
I like it.
Stylish, but manly.
What?
You wanna try mine?
That's not what I was...
You're not getting this.
Never mind.
"There's a free-trade zone just
south of the border into Mexico."
"Nafta created it."
"No tariffs, cheap materials,
cheap labor..."
"Products for the U.S. Market."
Now, the Qasimis own
a factory there.
That's where the girls
were dropped off
and then shipped out
to their new destinations
probably somewhere
in the Middle East.
Now, the Qasimis appear legit
but that doesn't mean they won't
have muscle at the factory.
Well, it's the border.
They'll have muscle.
"We're counting on that.
The Qasimis are smart."
"If we arrest them, they'll flip on whoever's
rounding up these girls in the U.S."
"that's the guy
we need to find."
You wanna give that to your bosses and tell
them we'd like to have a little chat?
Howdy. Uh, my name is,
uh, Patrick.
This is my head of security, Dennis.
You all must be, uh,
Ray and Ali.
Ray and Ali?
We don't know you.
Where did you get that?
Well, I own a couple of
gentlemen's clubs up in Houston.
Real exclusive...
you know, o-only the best.
Ramon...
he likes coming into my club.
He likes my girls.
He likes them all the way
to the poorhouse.
Who's Ramon?
I gotcha.
Uh, mum's the word, huh?
Here's the thing... Ramon gave me the truck
that this here gal came from.
Uh, this Ramon,
whoever he is...
Why would he do that...
just give you a truck?
Ramon had a little bit
of bad luck.
One of them girls ran off.
He thought he might have winged
her, but he never did find her.
And he got to thinking
that maybe the man in charge
would take it all amiss.
I figure
you guys know that man.
That's none
of your business.
- Continue.
- Ramon was scared.
He wanted to take
a long holiday.
Needed some cash,
so I obliged.
And in return, he gave me
that truck and all its cargo.
Is the cargo safe?
Well, a little weepy maybe.
Lot of runny makeup.
But sure, it's safe.
Well, suppose,
just for kicks
that we know Ramon
and we want that truck
and the cargo.
How much?
10 thou for the truck,
5 thou a head.
Come on. They're girls,
not racehorses.
- $1,000 a head.
- 3 thou.
- $2,000.
- Deal.
But you got to come across
the border and pick it up.
- No.
You deliver them to us.
No. No deal.
I'm a businessman.
I ain't no smuggler.
You want that truck,
you want its cargo
You come across the border,
and you pick it up.
How much further?
We're almost there now.
There she blows.
Give us the keys.
Sure.
Give me the money first.
- Whoa. That's ain't money.
- No, it's not.
I thought we were just businessmen.
This is business, right?
It's a tough business.
There's nothing in there.
FBI! You're under arrest!
Get down on the ground!
Right there!
Get down!
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
It's a tough business, isn't it?
- You look uncomfortable.
- Don't be.
We're here to help you.
Help?
You've killed me.
Just by bringing us here
my brother and I are already dead.
We're just about the only people
who can help you now.
No. You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
You people are amateurs
compared to him.
Who? Give us a name.
He will bury you.
- Well, we'll see about that.
- Yeah, you will.
You recognize this girl?
She's 16 years old.
My brother and me
will not say a word.
Maybe some time in gen pop
will loosen their tongues.
Maybe, but I don't
have high hopes.
I better go tell Daniela.
San Diego police
are on the line.
Put it on speaker.
This is agent Cho. You're
calling about Jesse O'connor?
"Yes, sir, but I'm sorry to tell
you we don't have good news."
- He wasn't there?
- "No, sir. He was there."
"Only thing is,
somebody else got him first."
- He's dead?
- "Yes, sir."
"Throat cut ear to ear.
I'm sending you a picture."
Thank you, officer. Please keep us
in the loop on your investigation.
Thanks. Bye.
You okay?
- Hello. Yes?
- "That thing in San Diego?"
"It's taken care of,
just so you know."
Jesse O'connor,
you mean?
Yep. He won't be an issue
for you anymore.
Good. Now we have another
problem I need you to fix.
Oh, yeah?
"The Qasimis."
A similar solution
would be greatly appreciated.
You got it, Mr. Ridley.
How soon you need it done?
Time is of the essence, Anthony.
Time is of the essence.
Okay.
"We didn't find your sister."
There was another truck.
She may have been on that.
So someone saw her
at the house?
Maybe.
We can't be sure.
But you will find her
and catch whoever's left, right?
You'll punish them
for what they've done?
We will.
I promise.
Well, she promised,
so now we have to.
"You, uh, need me to give you
a ride someplace?"
Oh, no, that's all right.
I already got one.
He was just waiting there
all the time?
Yeah.
Well, I guess those art-department guys
aren't that busy, huh?
It's the art-crimes department,
and he's very busy.
He just makes a point
to be there for me.
You really like this guy, huh?
He got a promotion.
It's a-a posting in D.C.
and he asked me
to go with him
So we can be together in D.C.
I'm thinking about it.
Yeah.
Hmm.
What do you think
about it?
Uh... I mean...
Congratulations, I guess.
Congratulations?
That's all
you're gonna say?
Sure. Well, I mean, if... if...
if that's... If that's what you want.
- You're not upset?
- No. Of course not.
I mean, if that's, um...
if you're happy.
Oh, I'm happy.
Then I'm happy.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Guess what. That show
we missed the other night...
They're playing another one
in 45 minutes.
We can catch it if... if...
you guys are done here, right?
- Oh, we're done. Yeah.
- Yeah. Sure.
- See you, Patrick.
- See you.